Henry A. Kissinger Papers, Part III: Guide to the Yale University Library Collection
Manuscripts and Archives
- Correspondence, 1941 - 2009; Series I
  - New York office
    - 2006
      - Bro-Bry, 2005 - 2006 (Box 117, Folder 3)
      - Bu, 2006 (Box 117, Folder 4)
      - Ca, 2006 (Box 117, Folder 5)
      - Cbn-Cha, 2002 - 2006 (Box 117, Folder 6)
      - Che, 2006 (Box 117, Folder 7)
      - Chi-Civ [includes photograph], 2006 (Box 117, Folder 8)
      - Cl-Cn, 2006 (Box 117, Folder 9)
      - Co-Cz, 2005 - 2006 (Box 117, Folder 10)
      - China, 2005 June-2006 June (Box 118, Folder 1)
      - China, 2006 July (Box 118, Folder 2)
      - China, 2006 August-October (Box 118, Folder 3)
      - China, 2006 November (Box 118, Folder 4)
      - CNN, 2006 (Box 118, Folder 5)
      - Dai-Dar, 2005 - 2006 (Box 118, Folder 6)
      - Das-Day, 2006 (Box 118, Folder 7)
      - Dea-Der, 2005 - 2006 (Box 118, Folder 8)
      - Des-Die, 2006 (Box 118, Folder 9)
      - Dio-Dzi, 1989 - 2006 (Box 118, Folder 10)
      - Dilenschneider, Robert L., 2005 December-2006 January (Box 118, Folder 11)
      - Dilenschneider, Robert L., 2006 March-2006 December (Box 118, Folder 12)
      - E, 2006 (Box 118, Folder 13)
      - Fa, 2006 (Box 118, Folder 14)
      - Fed-Fel, 2006 (Box 119, Folder 1)
      - Fer-Feu, 2006 (Box 119, Folder 2)
      - Fh-Fi, 2006 (Box 119, Folder 3)
      - Fl-Fp, 2006 (Box 119, Folder 4)
      - Fr-Fu, 2006 (Box 119, Folder 5)
      - Fox News, 2006 (Box 119, Folder 6)
      - Ga-Ge, 2005 - 2006 (Box 119, Folder 7)
      - Gf-Go, 2004 - 2006 (Box 119, Folder 8)
      - Gr, 2005 - 2006 (Box 119, Folder 9)
      - Gu-Gy, 2005 - 2006 (Box 119, Folder 10)
      - Haa-Ham, 2005 - 2006 (Box 119, Folder 11)
      - Han-Hbo, 2005 - 2006 (Box 119, Folder 12)
      - He, 2005 - 2006 (Box 120, Folder 1)
      - Hi, 2005 - 2006 (Box 120, Folder 2)
      - Ho, 2005 - 2007 (Box 120, Folder 3)
      - Hu, 2005 - 2006 (Box 120, Folder 4)
      - Ik-In, 2005 - 2006 (Box 120, Folder 5)
      - Ir-Iv, 1988, 2006; 2006 (Box 120, Folder 6)
      - Jac-Jaj, 2005 - 2006 (Box 120, Folder 7)
      - Jap-Jew, 2005 - 2006 (Box 120, Folder 8)
      - Jo [includes photographs], 2005 - 2006 (Box 120, Folder 9)
      - Ju, 2004 - 2006 (Box 120, Folder 10)
      - Ka, 2005 - 2006 (Box 121, Folder 1)
      - Ke, 2006 - 2007 (Box 121, Folder 2)
      - Ki-Km, 2005 - 2006 (Box 121, Folder 3)
      - Ko, 2004 - 2006 (Box 121, Folder 4)
      - Kr-Ky, 1974; 2006 (Box 121, Folder 5)
      - Lag-Lan, 2006 (Box 121, Folder 6)
      - Lar-Lda, 2006 (Box 121, Folder 7)
      - Lea-Lem, 2006 (Box 121, Folder 8)
      - Leo-Lew, 2005 - 2006 (Box 121, Folder 9)
      - Li-Lu, 2006 (Box 121, Folder 10)
      - Lavin, Franklin L., 2006 (Box 122, Folder 1)
      - Ma, 2004 - 2006 (Box 122, Folder 2)
      - Mc, 2005 - 2006 (Box 122, Folder 3)
      - Me, 2006 (Box 122, Folder 4)
      - Mi-Mo, 2006 (Box 122, Folder 5)
      - Ms-My, 2005 - 2006 (Box 122, Folder 6)
      - MacBain, Louise, 2006 (Box 122, Folder 7)
      - Manhattan Institute, 2006 (Box 122, Folder 8)
      - Na-Nb, 2006 (Box 122, Folder 9)
      - Neg-Neu, 2006 (Box 122, Folder 10)
      - New-Ney, 2006 (Box 123, Folder 1)
      - Nh-Ni, 2006 (Box 123, Folder 2)
      - No, 2006 (Box 123, Folder 3)
      - O, 2006 (Box 123, Folder 4)
      - Pa, 2006 (Box 123, Folder 5)
      - Pe, 2006 (Box 123, Folder 6)
      - Pf, 2006 (Box 123, Folder 7)
      - Ph-Pl, 2006 (Box 123, Folder 8)
      - Po-Pu, 2006 (Box 123, Folder 9)
      - Q, 2006 (Box 123, Folder 10)
      - Ra-Rb, 2005 - 2006 (Box 123, Folder 11)
      - Re-Ri, 2006 (Box 124, Folder 1)
      - Ro, 2006 (Box 124, Folder 2)
      - Ru-Ry, 2006 (Box 124, Folder 3)
      - Saba-Scha, 2006 (Box 124, Folder 4)
      - Sche-Schn, 2005 - 2007 (Box 124, Folder 5)
      - Scho-Schr, 2005 - 2006 (Box 124, Folder 6)
      - Schu-Schw, 2005 - 2006 (Box 124, Folder 7)
      - Sci-Sie, 2005 - 2006 (Box 124, Folder 8)
      - Sil-Ska, 2004 - 2006 (Box 124, Folder 9)
      - Sla-Som, 2005 - 2006 (Box 124, Folder 10)
      - Son-Spo, 2005 - 2006 (Box 124, Folder 11)
      - Sta-Sti [includes photograph], 2004 - 2006 (Box 125, Folder 1)
      - Sto-Sum, 2005 - 2006 (Box 125, Folder 2)
      - Sun-Sym, 2004 - 2006 (Box 125, Folder 3)
      - Shultz, George, 2006 (Box 125, Folder 4)
      - Simes, Dimitri K., 2006 (Box 125, Folder 5)
      - Ta-To, 2006 (Box 125, Folder 6)
      - Tr-Tw, 2006 (Box 125, Folder 7)
      - Time, 2006 (Box 125, Folder 8)
      - U, 2005 - 2006 (Box 125, Folder 9)
      - Va, 2005 - 2006 (Box 125, Folder 10)
      - Vi-Vo, 2005 - 2006 (Box 125, Folder 11)
      - Wa-Wb, 2005 - 2006 (Box 126, Folder 1)
      - Wea-Weh, 2006 (Box 126, Folder 2)
      - Wei-Wey, 2006 (Box 126, Folder 3)
      - Whita, 2006 (Box 126, Folder 4)
      - White House C-F, 2006 (Box 126, Folder 5)
      - Whitehe-Whittie, 2005 - 2006 (Box 126, Folder 6)
      - Wi, 2006 (Box 126, Folder 7)
      - Wn-Wt, 2005 - 2006 (Box 126, Folder 8)
      - White House, 2006 January-July (Box 126, Folder 9)
      - White House, 2006 August (Box 126, Folder 10)
      - X-Y, 2005 - 2006 (Box 126, Folder 11)
      - Z, 2006 (Box 126, Folder 12)
      - ZEIT-Stiftung, 2006 (Box 127, Folder 1)
    - 2007
      - Aa-Af, 2007 - 2008 (Box 127, Folder 2)
      - Ag-Aj, 2006 - 2007 (Box 127, Folder 3)
      - Akb-Alj, 2007 (Box 127, Folder 4)
      - Alf-All, 2006 - 2008 (Box 127, Folder 5)
      - Alt-Ama, 2007 (Box 127, Folder 6)
      - America-American F, 2007 - 2008 (Box 127, Folder 7)
      - American H-T, 2007 - 2008 (Box 127, Folder 8)
      - Americans-Americas, 2007 (Box 127, Folder 9)
      - And-Ang, 2007 (Box 127, Folder 10)
      - Ani-Ant, 2007 (Box 128, Folder 1)
      - Ap [includes photographs], 2007 (Box 128, Folder 2)
      - Ar, 2007 (Box 128, Folder 3)
      - As, 2007 (Box 128, Folder 4)
      - At-Az, 2007 (Box 128, Folder 5)
      - Advisory Council on International Affairs (AIV) [1 of 2], 2007 (Box 128, Folder 6)
      - Advisory Council on International Affairs (AIV) [2 of 2], 2007 (Box 128, Folder 7)
      - Akbar, M. J., 2007 (Box 128, Folder 8)
      - American Friends of Versailles, 2007 - 2008 (Box 128, Folder 9)
      - Bad-Baj, 2007 (Box 128, Folder 10)
      - Bak-Bar, 2007 (Box 128, Folder 11)
      - Bas-Bay, 2007 (Box 129, Folder 1)
      - Bea-Bei, 2007 (Box 129, Folder 2)
      - Bel, 2007 (Box 129, Folder 3)
      - Ben-Beu, 2007 - 2008 (Box 129, Folder 4)
      - Bh-Bi, 2006 - 2008 (Box 129, Folder 5)
      - Bla-Blo [includes photographs], 2006 - 2007 (Box 129, Folder 6)
      - Blu-Bnp, 2007 (Box 129, Folder 7)
      - Bo, 2007 - 2008 (Box 129, Folder 8)
      - Bra-Bri, 2007 - 2008 (Box 129, Folder 9)
      - Bro-Brz, 1999, 2007-2008; 2007 - 2008 (Box 130, Folder 1)
      - Buc-Bul [includes photographs], 2007 (Box 130, Folder 2)
      - Bur-Bus, 2007 - 2008 (Box 130, Folder 3)
      - BBC, 2007 - 2008 (Box 130, Folder 4)
      - Cab-Car, 2007 (Box 130, Folder 5)
      - Cas-Cct, 1969; 2007 (Box 130, Folder 6)
      - Ce, 2007 (Box 130, Folder 7)
      - Cha, 2007 (Box 130, Folder 8)
      - Cheb-Chin, 2006 - 2007 (Box 130, Folder 9)
      - China B-E, 2007 (Box 131, Folder 1)
      - China F-T, 2007 (Box 131, Folder 2)
      - Chine-Chira, 2007 (Box 131, Folder 3)
      - Cho-Chu, 2007 (Box 131, Folder 4)
      - Ci-Cn, 2007 (Box 131, Folder 5)
      - Coa-Coi, 2007 (Box 131, Folder 6)
      - Col-Com, 2007 (Box 131, Folder 7)
      - Con-Cot, 2007 - 2008 (Box 131, Folder 8)
      - Cou-Cru, 2007 - 2008 (Box 131, Folder 9)
      - Ct-Cz, 2007 (Box 131, Folder 10)
      - Carl Friedrich von Weizsäcker-Gesellschaft e.V., 2008 (Box 131, Folder 11)
      - China, 2006 - 2007 (Box 132, Folder 1)
      - Columbia University, 2007 (Box 132, Folder 2)
      - Confederation of Indian Industry (CII), 2007 (Box 132, Folder 3)
      - Da, 2007 (Box 132, Folder 4)
      - Dea-Del, 2007 (Box 132, Folder 5)
      - Dem-Dfg [includes photograph], 2007 (Box 132, Folder 6)
      - Di, 2007 - 2008 (Box 132, Folder 7)
      - Do, 2004 - 2007 (Box 132, Folder 8)
      - Dr, 2007 (Box 132, Folder 9)
      - Du-Dz, 2006 - 2007 (Box 132, Folder 10)
      - Dilenschneider, Robert L., 2007 January-September (Box 132, Folder 11)
      - Dilenschneider, Robert L., 2007 October-December (Box 132, Folder 12)
      - Ea-Eb, 2007 (Box 133, Folder 1)
      - Ec-Ei, 2007 - 2008 (Box 133, Folder 2)
      - Ek-El, 2007 (Box 133, Folder 3)
      - Em-Ex, 2007 - 2008 (Box 133, Folder 4)
      - Economic Club of New York, 2007 (Box 133, Folder 5)
      - Fai-Fel [includes photograph], 2007 (Box 133, Folder 6)
      - Fen-Feu, 2007 (Box 133, Folder 7)
      - Fi, 2007 (Box 133, Folder 8)
      - Fl, 2007 (Box 133, Folder 9)
      - Fol-Fon, 2007 (Box 133, Folder 10)
      - For-Fou, 2007 (Box 134, Folder 1)
      - Fox, 2007 (Box 134, Folder 2)
      - Fra-Fre, 2007 (Box 134, Folder 3)
      - Fri-Fut, 2007 (Box 134, Folder 4)
      - Fox News-polls, 2007 (Box 134, Folder 5)
      - French-American Foundation, 2007 (Box 134, Folder 6)
      - Ga, 2007 (Box 134, Folder 7)
      - Ge-Gf, 2007 (Box 134, Folder 8)
      - Gi-Gl, 2007 (Box 134, Folder 9)
      - Gol-Gop, 2007 (Box 135, Folder 1)
      - Gor-Gov, 2007 (Box 135, Folder 2)
      - Gra, 2007 (Box 135, Folder 3)
      - Gre, 2007 (Box 135, Folder 4)
      - Gri-Gyl, 2007 (Box 135, Folder 5)
      - Haa-Hag, 2007 (Box 135, Folder 6)
      - Hal [includes photograph], 2007 (Box 135, Folder 7)
      - Ham-Han, 2007 (Box 135, Folder 8)
      - Har [includes photograph], 2007 (Box 135, Folder 9)
      - Haw-Haz, 2007 (Box 135, Folder 10)
      - Hea-Hen, 2007 (Box 135, Folder 11)
      - Her-Hes, 2007 (Box 135, Folder 12)
      - Hi, 2007 (Box 136, Folder 1)
      - Hoc-Hoo, 2007 (Box 136, Folder 2)
      - Hop, 2007 (Box 136, Folder 3)
      - Hor, 2007 (Box 136, Folder 4)
      - Hos-How, 2007 (Box 136, Folder 5)
      - Hs-Hy, 2007 (Box 136, Folder 6)
      - Halstead, Ted, 2007 (Box 136, Folder 7)
      - Horne, Alistair and Sheelin, 2007 (Box 136, Folder 8)
      - Ige-Ins, 2007 - 2008 (Box 136, Folder 9)
      - Int-Inv, 2007 (Box 136, Folder 10)
      - Ir-Is, 2007 (Box 137, Folder 1)
      - It-Iv, 2006 - 2008 (Box 137, Folder 2)
      - Jac-Jan, 1974, 2006-2008; 2006 - 2008 (Box 137, Folder 3)
      - Jap-Jav, 2004 - 2007 (Box 137, Folder 4)
      - Je-Ji, 1969, 2005-2007; 2005 - 2007 (Box 137, Folder 5)
      - Jo [includes photograph], 2005 - 2007 (Box 137, Folder 6)
      - Jp-Ju, 2006 - 2007 (Box 137, Folder 7)
      - Jewish People Policy Planning (JPPI), 2007 (Box 137, Folder 8)
      - Kag-Kam, 2006 - 2008 (Box 138, Folder 1)
      - Kar-Kaz [includes photographs], 2006 - 2007 (Box 138, Folder 2)
      - Ke-Kh, 2002 - 2007 (Box 138, Folder 3)
      - Ki, 2005 - 2007 (Box 138, Folder 4)
      - Kl, 2007 - 2008 (Box 138, Folder 5)
      - Kob-Kop, 1986; 2007 - 2008 (Box 138, Folder 6)
      - Kor-Kos, 2007 (Box 138, Folder 7)
      - Kov-Koz, 2007 (Box 138, Folder 8)
      - Kr-Ky, 2007 (Box 138, Folder 9)
      - Laf-Laq, 2007 (Box 138, Folder 10)
      - Lar-Lay, 2007 (Box 139, Folder 1)
      - Lea-Lem, 2007 (Box 139, Folder 2)
      - Leo, 2007 (Box 139, Folder 3)
      - Les-Lew, 2006 - 2008 (Box 139, Folder 4)
      - Li, 2007 (Box 139, Folder 5)
      - Lib-Lie, 2007 (Box 139, Folder 6)
      - Lig-Liv, 2007 (Box 139, Folder 7)
      - Lo, 2007 (Box 139, Folder 8)
      - Lu, 2007 (Box 139, Folder 9)
      - Ly-Ma, 2007 (Box 139, Folder 10)
      - Maa-Mal, 2006 - 2007 (Box 139, Folder 11)
      - Man, 2007 (Box 139, Folder 12)
      - Mar-Mas, 2007 (Box 140, Folder 1)
      - Mat-Mau, 2007 (Box 140, Folder 2)
      - Mcc-Mcf, 2007 (Box 140, Folder 3)
      - Mcg-Mcn, 2007 (Box 140, Folder 4)
      - Md, 2007 (Box 140, Folder 5)
      - Mea-Mem, 2007 (Box 140, Folder 6)
      - Men-Mey, 2007 (Box 140, Folder 7)
      - Mi-Mj, 2006 - 2007 (Box 140, Folder 8)
      - Mod-Mon, 2007 (Box 140, Folder 9)
      - Mor, 2007 (Box 140, Folder 10)
      - Mos-Msn, 2007 (Box 140, Folder 11)
      - Mu-My, 2006 - 2007 (Box 140, Folder 12)
      - McCaffrey, Barry R., 2007 May-September (Box 141, Folder 1)
      - McCaffrey, Barry R., 2007 October (Box 141, Folder 2)
      - McCaffrey, Barry R., 2007 December (Box 141, Folder 3)
      - Morris, Dick, 2007 (Box 141, Folder 4)
      - Naac-Nath, 2007 - 2008 (Box 141, Folder 5)
      - National A-B, 2007 (Box 141, Folder 6)
      - National C, 2007 (Box 141, Folder 7)
      - National D-J, 2007 (Box 141, Folder 8)
      - National M-W, 2007 (Box 141, Folder 9)
      - Nav-Neu, 2007 (Box 141, Folder 10)
      - New D-O, 2007 (Box 141, Folder 11)
      - New York A-S, 2007 - 2008 (Box 142, Folder 1)
      - New York T-New Yorker, 2007 (Box 142, Folder 2)
      - Ney-Niv, 2007 (Box 142, Folder 3)
      - Noa-Noo, 2007 (Box 142, Folder 4)
      - Nor-Nou, 2007 (Box 142, Folder 5)
      - Nuc-Nue, 2007 (Box 142, Folder 6)
      - Nun-Nuz, 2007 (Box 142, Folder 7)
      - Ob-Ol, 2007 (Box 142, Folder 8)
      - On-Or, 2007 (Box 142, Folder 9)
      - Os-Oz, 2006 - 2007 (Box 142, Folder 10)
      - Pac-Par, 2007 (Box 142, Folder 11)
      - Pas-Pbs, 2007 (Box 143, Folder 1)
      - Pe, 2007 (Box 143, Folder 2)
      - Ph, 2007 (Box 143, Folder 3)
      - Pi, 2007 (Box 143, Folder 4)
      - Pl, 2007 (Box 143, Folder 5)
      - Po, 2006 - 2007 (Box 143, Folder 6)
      - Pr-Pu, 2007 (Box 143, Folder 7)
      - Py, 2007 (Box 143, Folder 8)
      - Q, 2007 (Box 143, Folder 9)
      - Ra, 2007 (Box 143, Folder 10)
      - Re-Rh [includes photograph], 2006 - 2007 (Box 143, Folder 11)
      - Ri, 2007 (Box 143, Folder 12)
      - Rob-Roc, 2007 - 2009 (Box 144, Folder 1)
      - Rog-Roo, 2007 (Box 144, Folder 2)
      - Ros-Rot, 2007 (Box 144, Folder 3)
      - Ru-Ry, 2007 (Box 144, Folder 4)
      - Rodman, Peter W., 2007 (Box 144, Folder 5)
      - Rosenbaum, Richard M., 2007 (Box 144, Folder 6)
      - Russia, 2007 (Box 144, Folder 7)
      - Sab-Sal [includes photographs], 2007 (Box 144, Folder 8)
      - Sam-Sav, 2007 (Box 144, Folder 9)
      - Scha-Schl, 2007 (Box 145, Folder 1)
      - Schm [includes photographs], 2007 (Box 145, Folder 2)
      - Schn-Scho [includes photographs], 2007 - 2008 (Box 145, Folder 3)
      - Schu, 2007 (Box 145, Folder 4)
      - Schw-Scow, 2007 (Box 145, Folder 5)
      - Se, 2007 (Box 145, Folder 6)
      - Sha-Shp, 2006 - 2007 (Box 145, Folder 7)
      - Shu-Sie, 2007 (Box 145, Folder 8)
      - Sil-Sit, 2007 (Box 145, Folder 9)
      - Sk, 2007 (Box 145, Folder 10)
      - Sl, 2007 (Box 145, Folder 11)
      - Sm-Sn [includes photograph], 2007 (Box 146, Folder 1)
      - So [includes photographs], 2007 (Box 146, Folder 2)
      - Sp-Sr, 2005 - 2007 (Box 146, Folder 3)
      - Sta, 2007 (Box 146, Folder 4)
      - Ste-Sto, 2006 - 2007 (Box 146, Folder 5)
      - Str-Sul, 2007 (Box 146, Folder 6)
      - Sun, 2007 - 2008 (Box 146, Folder 7)
      - Sur-Swi, 2007 (Box 146, Folder 8)
      - Simes, Dimitri K., 2007 (Box 146, Folder 9)
      - Slaughter, Anne-Marie, 2006 - 2007 (Box 146, Folder 10)
      - T, 2007 (Box 146, Folder 11)
      - Ta-Te, 2006 - 2007 (Box 146, Folder 12)
      - Tha-Tre, 2007 - 2008 (Box 147, Folder 1)
      - Tri-Twe, 2007 (Box 147, Folder 2)
      - Uci-Une, 2007 (Box 147, Folder 3)
      - Unit, 2007 (Box 147, Folder 4)
      - Univ, 2007 - 2008 (Box 147, Folder 5)
      - Ur-Us, 2007 (Box 147, Folder 6)
      - Va-Ve, 2007 (Box 147, Folder 7)
      - Vi, 2007 (Box 147, Folder 8)
      - Vo-Vt, 2007 (Box 147, Folder 9)
      - W, 2007 (Box 147, Folder 10)
      - Wag-War, 2007 (Box 147, Folder 11)
      - Was-Wat, 2007 (Box 147, Folder 12)
      - We, 2007 (Box 148, Folder 1)
      - Wh, 2007 (Box 148, Folder 2)
      - Wi, 2006 - 2007 (Box 148, Folder 3)
      - Wol-Woo, 2007 - 2008 (Box 148, Folder 4)
      - Wor, 2006 - 2007 (Box 148, Folder 5)
      - Woz-Wyl, 2007 (Box 148, Folder 6)
      - Wanandi, Jusuf, 2007 (Box 148, Folder 7)
      - Wehner, Peter, 2007 January-July (Box 148, Folder 8)
      - Wehner, Peter, 2007 August-October (Box 148, Folder 9)
      - White Nights Foundation, 2006 (Box 148, Folder 10)
      - White Nights Foundation, 2007 (Box 148, Folder 11)
      - X, 2007 (Box 148, Folder 12)
      - Y, 2007 (Box 149, Folder 1)
      - Za, 2007 (Box 149, Folder 2)
      - Zd-Zu, 2007 (Box 149, Folder 3)
      - Zogby Poll, 2007 (Box 149, Folder 4)
      - Unidentified, 2007 (Box 149, Folder 5)
  - White House personal file
    - Messages received, P, 1968 - 1973 (Box 150, Folder 1)
    - Messages received, Q, 1969 (Box 150, Folder 2)
    - Messages received, R, 1968 - 1973 (Box 150, Folder 3)
    - Messages received, Sa-Sh, 1967 - 1973 (Box 150, Folder 4)
    - Messages received, Si-Sp, 1968 - 1975 (Box 150, Folder 5)
    - Messages received, St-Sz, 1968 - 1973 (Box 150, Folder 6)
    - Messages received, T, 1968 - 1973 (Box 150, Folder 7)
    - Messages received, U, 1968 - 1973 (Box 150, Folder 8)
    - Messages received, V, 1968 - 1973 (Box 150, Folder 9)
    - Messages received, Wa, 1968 - 1973 (Box 150, Folder 10)
    - Messages received, We-Wi, 1968 - 1973 (Box 150, Folder 11)
    - Messages received, Wo-Wy, 1968 - 1973 (Box 150, Folder 12)
    - Messages received, X-Z, 1968 - 1973 (Box 151, Folder 1)
    - Messages sent, Ab-Be, 1969 - 1974 (Box 151, Folder 2)
    - Messages sent, Bl-Cu, 1969 - 1974 (Box 151, Folder 3)
    - Messages sent, Da-El, 1969 - 1973 (Box 151, Folder 4)
    - Messages sent, Es-Gu, 1969 - 1973 (Box 151, Folder 5)
    - Messages sent, H-K, 1969 - 1973 (Box 151, Folder 6)
    - Messages sent, La-Os, 1957; 1969 - 1973 (Box 151, Folder 7)
    - Messages sent, Pa-Pr, 1969 - 1973 (Box 151, Folder 8)
    - Messages sent, Qu-Sn, 1968 - 1973 (Box 151, Folder 9)
    - Messages sent, Sp-Tr, 1969 - 1973 (Box 151, Folder 10)
    - Messages sent, U-Z, 1969 - 1973 (Box 151, Folder 11)
    - Nab-Net, 1968 - 1973 (Box 151, Folder 12)
    - Neu-Nus, 1969 - 1975 (Box 152, Folder 1)
    - Newspapers and clippings, Feb 8-May 31, 1969, 1968 - 1969 (Box 152, Folder 2)
    - Newspapers and clippings, Jun 1-Dec 31, 1969, 1965 - 1969 (Box 152, Folder 3)
    - Newspapers and clippings, Jan 1-May 31, 1970, 1969 - 1970 (Box 152, Folder 4)
    - Newspapers and clippings, Jun 1-Dec 31, 1970 [1 of 2] (Box 152, Folder 5)
    - Newspapers and clippings, Jun 1-Dec 31, 1970 [2 of 2] (Box 152, Folder 6)
    - Newspapers and clippings, 1971-1973 [1 of 2], 1970 - 1973 (Box 152, Folder 7)
    - Newspapers and clippings, 1971-1973 [2 of 2], 1970 - 1973 (Box 152, Folder 8)
- Subject Files, 1958 - 2007; Series II
  The subject files address a variety of topics related to international affairs with which Kissinger involved himself, primarily after he left government service in 1977 through 2004. Major topics include Christopher Hitchens’ writings about Kissinger and Congressional hearings held in 1992 on prisoners of war and missing in action (POW/MIA) from the Vietnam War at which Kissinger testified. Of particular note are Kissinger’s handwritten notes and typescripts of the notes from his discussions with Soviet leaders, including Mikhail Gorbachev and Andrei Gromyko, during his 1987 visit to the Soviet Union. Some of the files on other topics may have been used by Kissinger for various writing projects, but research files clearly associated with specific writing projects can be found in Series V.
  The minority of files that contain material from Kissinger’s years of government service consist mainly of copies of government documents and publications relevant to the topic although there is a small amount of original material from this period including Kissinger’s short handwritten notes to Richard Nixon from the president’s visit to China in 1972 and a 1961 letter from John F. Kennedy, Jr. welcoming Kissinger to his administration as a consultant. In addition, the Peter W. Rodman files include a number of original memoranda of conversation from Kissinger’s time in office. These memoranda record Kissinger’s discussions, primarily with journalists and business and church leaders. Copies of these memoranda may be available at the National Archives and Records Administration (NARA). Memoranda of conversation are often especially informative documents because they provide detailed summaries or near verbatim accounts written to document specific conversations.
  The Nixon tapes partial transcripts are another detailed source on Kissinger’s work in the Nixon White House. These files contain transcripts that intended to relate every conversation that the Nixon White House tapes recorded in which Kissinger was a participant. These partial transcripts from 1971 to 1973 usually provide word by word accounts although sometimes material is summarized. Since a single consultant hired by the private Nixon Foundation created all the transcripts and the original, untranscribed Nixon White House tapes available at the Nixon Presidential Library are often difficult to hear, the accuracy of the transcripts found in these files is difficult to judge.
  Similar subject files covering roughly the same period can be in the Henry A. Kissinger Papers, Part II.
  Series II is arranged alphabetically by subject.
  - "Age of Uncertainty," BBC [1 of 2], 1976, undated (Box 154, Folder 1)
  - "Age of Uncertainty," BBC [2 of 2], 1976, undated (Box 154, Folder 2)
  - Arms control and USSR, 1987 - 1988 (Box 154, Folder 3)
  - Bayerisches Fernsehen interview-correspondence, 1995 (Box 154, Folder 4)
  - Berlin crisis, 1958-1961-research by William Hyland [1 of 2], 1958 - 1981; 1992 (Box 154, Folder 5)
  - Berlin crisis, 1958-1961-research by William Hyland [2 of 2], 1959 - 1981; 1992 (Box 154, Folder 6)
  - Botha, R. F., 1977 (Box 154, Folder 7)
  - "The Carter Record," Public Affairs Department, Republican National Committee, 1980 (Box 154, Folder 8)
  - China trip-original notes to Richard Nixon, 1972 February (Box 154, Folder 9)
  - Corbis Sygma, 1999 (Box 154, Folder 10)
  - Cuba-Peter Kornbluh, 1994 - 1997; 1975 (Box 154, Folder 11)
  - De Gaulle, Charles-documentary interview correspondence, 1987 (Box 154, Folder 12)
  - File management of early career papers
    - A series, Circa 1977 (Box 154, Folder 13)
    - B series, Circa 1977 (Box 154, Folder 14)
    - C series, Circa 1977 (Box 154, Folder 15)
    - D series, Circa 1977 (Box 154, Folder 16)
    - E series, Circa 1977 (Box 154, Folder 17)
    - F series, Circa 1977 (Box 154, Folder 18)
    - G series, Circa 1977 (Box 154, Folder 19)
    - H series, Circa 1977 (Box 154, Folder 20)
    - J series, Circa 1977 (Box 154, Folder 21)
    - Library of Congress, 1986 (Box 154, Folder 22)
  - Film project Metternich based on A World Restored [1 of 2], 1993 - 1994 (Box 155, Folder 1)
  - Film project Metternich based on A World Restored [2 of 2], 1993 - 1994 (Box 155, Folder 2)
  - Foreign policy themes in Bill Clinton's public statements, 1994 (Box 155, Folder 3)
  - Gag memoranda, 1972 - 1974; 1989 (Box 155, Folder 4)
  - Georgetown University faculty appointment-press clippings, 1977 (Box 155, Folder 5)
  - Greater New York Hospital Association tribute to Paul Marks-correspondence, 1997 (Box 155, Folder 6)
  - Haldeman, H. R.-columns, 1976 (Box 155, Folder 7)
  - Hitchens (Christopher) controversy [1 of 5], 1968 - 1979; 2001 (Box 155, Folder 8)
  - Hitchens (Christopher) controversy [2 of 5], 1968 - 1979; 2001 (Box 155, Folder 9)
  - Hitchens (Christopher) controversy [3 of 5], 1968 - 1979; 2001 (Box 155, Folder 10)
  - Hitchens (Christopher) controversy [4 of 5], 1968 - 1979; 2001 (Box 156, Folder 1)
  - Hitchens (Christopher) controversy [5 of 5], 1968 - 1979; 2001 (Box 156, Folder 2)
  - Hostages and Jimmy Carter, Circa 1979-circa 1980 (Box 156, Folder 3)
  - Kennedy, John F.-correspondence, 1961 (Box 156, Folder 4)
  - Korea investigations, 1970 - 1978 (Box 156, Folder 5)
  - Kurds, 1974 - 1980 (Box 156, Folder 6)
  - Mexico-press clippings, 1973 (Box 156, Folder 7)